It's been a while.
You've been well, right?
All right, let's get going.
This taxi has
two rules.
I occasionally pick up new passengers,
but I mostly drive regulars
who book in advance.
On the way to their destination,
we listen together
to whatever music they want.
'A Song Just for You'
You wonder if I make enough for gas
only driving regulars?
More people seek out this taxi
than you'd think.
There's Gyehyang, who can't sleep
because of insomnia.
Changshik, who only wears
clothes others have thrown away.
And even Ma Dae-il,
the long-haired barista.
Oh, and in the drama,
the actress Oh Young-ran,
who plays Matsogeum,
is a regular in this taxi, too.
As we drive along,
I take song requests from my passengers.
Sometimes their stories
become the lyrics.
Sir!
Huh?
Every time they get in the back seat,
some passengers make a full confession.
Come to think of it, sometimes it's easier
to open up to someone
you're not too close to
and tell them what's really on your mind.
In that sense,
the driver's seat and
the passenger's back seat
make for just the right distance.
What do I do when I don't have a booking?
Well...
I kill time somewhere
while I wait for a booking.
I wait for bookings while I eat.
Oh, this one, this one, this one.
Look, look, look!
I wait for bookings
while coaching the players.
I wait for bookings,
savoring the aroma of coffee.
Yeon-woo?
This is Yeon-woo,
one of my regulars.
Whenever she goes through a breakup,
she books a taxi.
Every time I pick her up,
my heart feels heavy.
Driver...
Just take me anywhere.
Today...
Did she break up again?
You changed your hair.
Short hair suits you, too.
Thank you.
I was wondering...
Did you cut your hair
because of a breakup...?
He's the absolute worst.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said
something so... so insensitive.
No, I mean...
That jerk is the absolute worst.
Hurry up, babe!
What? You bought four?
I didn't know which flavor you'd like.
These are cinnamon—one with
sugar, one without.
- These are chocolate, one with sugar.
- Oh, my!
And one without.
Pick whichever one you want most.
I'll eat the rest.
Oh, stop it.
I'm gonna cry.
Oh, what are you saying?
Come on.
Hey, Teddy,
could you carry these two for me?
Thanks.
Teddy?
Okay, I'll take it.
Oh...
Like an idiot...
Getting stuck taking a commemorative
photo between those two...
Ugh, this is so annoying.
It's only been three days
since he broke up with me.
Could you take one vertically, too?
One, two...
- Huh? Uh, uh...
- Oh, huh?
Huh.
Oh, what was that?
I don't know.
We've arrived.
Where are we?
The zoo.
This place suits me.
Driver.
Could you wait here for a little while?
Oh, goodness. Oh, goodness.
- Oh, dear, oh, dear.
- Oh...
- It's okay.
- Someone might think...
we're kidnapping a bear from the zoo.
Actually, I was walking
around in this earlier...
I hurriedly took it off in case someone
shot me with a tranquilizer dart.
Oh, that was really dangerous.
- Exactly.
There, all cleaned up?
Oh.
There's a pocket for personal
items inside this mascot suit.
You know, my phone, makeup...
I've got lots of candy in there, too,
for when my blood sugar dips at work.
Oh...
He said he liked short hair.
So I cut mine.
But the woman I saw him with
today had long, straight hair.
He said women with long, straight hair looked
like ghosts, so he wouldn't even look at them.
And he'd only give me
perfume in scents he liked.
I hate musk.
- Yeon-woo.
- Yeah?
I'm the one who has to smell
it, after all.
So I realized I should
pick a scent I like.
Yeah.
I'm always trying to
accommodate the other person.
I really try hard, you know?
But today, it suddenly hit me.
'Oh...'
'Maybe I only cared about being who
the other person wanted me to be.'
Maybe that man
has never seen the real you, Yeon-woo.
What I like...
and what I don't like.
I've never tried to show
him who I really am,
just as I am.
I was afraid he'd hate the real me.
Even when I was dating, I was always
hiding deep inside that bear costume.
Driver.
I'd like to hear this song today.
Oh, The Black Skirts are great!
You know The Black Skirts?
I have a pretty broad musical range.
I always buy The Black Skirts' albums.
Though they don't put
out albums very often.
No, I always kept you in mind, Driver,
and asked for songs I thought you'd know.
Yes, I noticed you always did that.
It honestly made me feel a little hurt.
Here.
Ta-da!
♪ By tomorrow ♪
♪ The people who'll leave me ♪
♪ Aren't who I'm worried ♪
♪ About ♪
♪ By tomorrow ♪
♪ I'll be across the sea again ♪
♪ Left all alone ♪
♪ Will you be all right? ♪
♪ Into my ear ♪
♪ Sing a song for me ♪
♪ So I won't hear ♪
♪ The other birds sing ♪
♪ My one and only ♪
♪ Love, as I leave it behind ♪
♪ The handkerchief ♪
♪ You'd kept hidden, wave goodbye ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Hey, let your bright light
shine on me ♪
♪ Can you love me
unconditionally? ♪
♪ And sing a million lullabies
on a sleepy day ♪
♪ Hey, let your sea breeze
blow on me ♪
♪ When I am sailing
internationally ♪
♪ And whisper... ♪
Oh? Driver,
not right in front of my house.
Could you drop me off
up there instead?
- Right there, here.
- Uh...
Yes.
Huh?
I said I'd get out here?
Well, earlier at the zoo,
I left the meter running,
and the fare really piled up.
Oh! I'll cover the dryer, too.
Oh...
D-Driver, the fare must've
been pretty high today, right?
Yes.
You could probably take tomorrow off
and not accept any bookings.
Oh, dear.
What should I say?
Just...
Tell them exactly what happened.
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry.
Yes, yes. I'm sorry.
Yes.
Oh...
First,
they said to return that teddy bear first.
What, do they think I'll run
off without returning it?
If I get fired,
I'll just find another part-time job.
I don't want to...
wear a mascot costume anymore.
Yes.
Thank you.
All right.
Cheers!
Okay, let's take the palace.
Aw, come on.
Oh! Uh, uh, uh, uh!
K-K-Knight... oh...
Whoa!
Checkmate!
- Check! Check! Take that!
- Damn it.
Aw...
All right. Ha ha.
Oh, damn.
A regular of mine, and
a collector of breakups,
Yeon-woo, is calling.
What kind of breakup
has she had this time?
I've heard a lot about you.
Yeon-woo said you've helped her a lot whenever
she's been going through a hard time.
Oh.
Oh, it was nothing.
I just make sure she gets home
safely, that's all.
For some reason,
I wanted you to meet my boyfriend, sir.
You know my whole story
better than anyone.
Well...
What do you think?
Doesn't this one seem like it'll last?
If things always went the way I said,
I'd be a fortune-teller,
not a taxi driver.
Come on, you must have a gut feeling.
My gut says it's looking good.
And you're even going on a
weekend date at an amusement park.
Mm-hmm.
We're heading to work.
We're coworkers dating.
Oh?
Oh, so you're still
wearing the mascot costume?
No, I ditched the mascot costume.
That day,
I took your advice and was
honest about everything,
and told my manager the whole truth.
So my manager switched
me to a different role.
Thanks to that,
I got to meet my honey here, too.
Hee-hee!
Oh!
All right, everyone...
What's the part everyone's been
waiting for at Black Hole 2000?
Dance time!
We're going to get started now.
Let's go!
♪ Hol, hol, Black Hole
Fly away, Black Hole ♪
♪ Spinning round as you go in,
coming out with a big grin ♪
♪ Hol, hol, Black Hole
Fly away, Black Hole ♪
♪ The two of you side by side ♪
♪ Heart-pounding Black Hole ♪
♪ Hol, hol, Black Hole
Fly away, Black Hole ♪
♪ Fall in love, Black Hole
Forever love, Black Hole ♪
♪ Hol, hol, Black Hole ♪
♪ Holololol, Black Hole ♪
Let's go!
Ho, ho!
Uh, aren't we setting off?
All right.
Let's keep this energy going
and set off.
Let's go!
Bye!
Ho!
Wow.
♪ By tomorrow ♪
♪ The ones who'll leave me behind ♪
♪ I'm not worried ♪
♪ About them ♪
♪ By tomorrow ♪
♪ I'll be across the sea again ♪
♪ Left all alone ♪
♪ Will you be all right? ♪
♪ Into my ear ♪
♪ Sing a song for me ♪
♪ So I won't hear ♪
♪ The calls of other birds ♪
♪ As I leave behind ♪
♪ The only love I've ever known ♪
♪ Wave the handkerchief ♪
♪ You kept hidden away ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Hey, let your bright light
shine on me ♪
♪ Can you love me
unconditionally? ♪
♪ And sing a million lullabies
on a sleepy day ♪
♪ Hey, let your sea breeze
blow on me ♪
♪ When I'm sailing
across the seas ♪
♪ And whisper all your prayers
on a stormy day ♪
♪ Into your mouth ♪
♪ I breathed my breath ♪
♪ Whenever that little heart ♪
♪ Sank in your chest ♪
♪ By tomorrow ♪
♪ You won't even be able to hold me back ♪
♪ Left all alone ♪
♪ Will you be all right? ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Hey, let your bright light
shine on me ♪
♪ Can you love me
unconditionally? ♪
♪ And sing a million lullabies
on a sleepy day ♪
♪ Hey, let your sea breeze
blow on me ♪
♪ When I'm sailing
internationally ♪
♪ And whisper all your prayers
on a stormy day ♪
♪ Hey, don't let your eyes turn red ♪
♪ When the day comes that we meet again ♪
♪ I want us to grow old together ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I promise you ♪
♪ Hey, let your bright light
shine on me ♪
♪ Can you love me
unconditionally? ♪
♪ And sing a million lullabies
on a sleepy day ♪